Thank you.
Hello.
Hello, can you hear my voice?
I love this poor
Hello, Vespaar.
Hello
So, will you be so kind to tell me about the way?
I have been doing a few things
I would write a sabbath
I mean
what do you think about stars in the sky and the sunrise during the moonlight
that never happens
Are you sure about the transcription?
no I mean
in the transcription
well done, bye
Hello, this bird.
I mean no no that's not I mean
Can you be specific
about the current situation in my life.
I
Think there has been some kind of mistake that I believe I
I believe that nothing can be better than life if it is life than it is life I don't
think about
i think another then the the the the the the the the the the the the what the
the
If you know me, then tell me about my story.
Thank you, my brother.
Thank you.
.
Hello, I'm back.
Thank you.
Yeah.
C'mon!
What a good!
I love you!
C'mon!
Thank you.
Ah!
All right.
and
Thank you.
Ah.
...
Thank you.